https://www.mrftyres.com//privacy-policy

We use cookies to offer you a better browsing experience. By using our site, you consent to our use of cookies. For more information, click here
Okay
X
THERE MAY BE SEVERAL FAKE WEBSITES IN PUBLIC DOMAIN CLAIMING TO BE WEBSITES OF
MRF LTD. AND PLACING ADVERTISMENTS FOR DEALERSHIPS, JOBS, ETC. WITH THE PURPOSE
OF EXTRACTING MONEY / PERSONAL DETAILS. MRF LTD. HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH SUCH
WEB SITES NOR DO WE COLLECT MONEY FOR THE PURPOSE OF DEALERSHIPS OR JOBS.
ANYBODY RESPONDING TO SUCH ADVERTISEMENTS SHALL BE DOING SO AT THEIR OWN RISK
AND WE REQUEST GENERAL PUBLIC TO EXERCISE CAUTION.
ALL OUR OFFICIAL E-MAIL ADDRESSES ORIGINATE FROM THE DOMAIN NAME mrfmail.com
FOR ANY INFORMATION AND CLARIFICATION, PLEASE REACH OUT TO US AT write2us@mrfmail.com
PRIVACY POLICY
General Statement:
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. This privacy statement explains our policies and practices regarding on-line customer information. It is through this disclosure that we intend to provide you with a level of comfort and confidence in how we collect, use, and safeguard personal and other information we collect or that you provide through this website, and how you can contact us if you have any questions or concerns. It is our sincere hope that by explaining our data handling practices we will develop a trusting and long-lasting relationship with you.
Information About Our Organization and Website:
This Privacy Statement applies to www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com. www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com are owned and maintained by ExperienceCommerce, Mumbai, on behalf of MRF LIMITED, New No. 114 (old No. 124)Greams Road, Chennai 600 006. India.
The business purpose of this website is to keep the users updated with the happenings at MRF Ltd and their various products.
Personally Identifiable Information We Collect From You:
During a visit to our site, no personally identifiable information about you is collected through any means or data flow channels.
Other (Non-Personally Identifiable) Information We Collect From Site Visitors:
During a normal visit to our site, no personally identifiable information about you is collected.All information on our site is free to browse at your leisure without the need for you to provide us with any personally identifiable information. www.mrftyres.com collects other information, non-personally identifiable information from site visitors. This means that we do not track these items on an individual basis that identifies the site visitor, but rather gather and collect this information on an aggregate or anonymous basis that includes all site visitors. Non-personal information includes tracking the site pages that are visited or the amount of time spent on our site.
Our primary goal in collecting aggregate information from you is to be able to perform site metrics that allow us to improve the
functionality of the website. We need to collect aggregate information in order to track page visits.
We may use session or persistent "cookies," and a third-party click tracking analytics tool, to collect aggregate or other non-personally identifiable information about site visitors. An explanation for each of these items and how they work is included in Section: Methods We Use to Collect Information.
How We Use the Aggregate or Non-Personally Identifiable Information We Collect:
Non-Personally identifiable information collected on www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com may be used to : Compile aggregate and statistical data to help in website design and to identify popular features Measure site activity to allow us to update our site to better meet user wants and needs.
www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com utilizes non-personal data for the purpose of performing analytics on the
users' experience while visiting this site. This analysis: Is performed on an aggregate level and does not identify you or your information personally Involves the use of a third party vendor acting on behalf of www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com are performed in order to improve our website and the user experience. This may include the use of session and/or persistent cookies to track user movement across this website or to track other events within or across this website. Any information that is provided to the third party vendors is to be used only for the purpose of performing the analytics and compiling reports of the data. The third party vendor is restricted from using this data in any other way other than to provide these services to MRF Limited and they may not share or resell this data.
Methods We Use to Collect Information
A "cookie" is a small text file that helps us in many ways to make your visit to our website more enjoyable and meaningful to you. For example, cookies avoid you having to log in every time you come back to one of our websites. They also allow us to tailor a website or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. There are a couple different types of cookies.
A "session" cookie is stored only in your computer's working memory (RAM) and only lasts for your browsing session. When you close all your browser's windows, or when you shut down your computer, the session cookie disappears forever.
A "persistent" cookie is stored on your computer's hard drive until a specified date, which could be tomorrow, next week, or 10 years from now. Persistent cookies stay on your computer until either a) they expire,) they are overwritten with newer cookies, c) you manually remove them. Most browsers can be configured not to accept cookies, however, this may prevent you from having access to some site functions or features.
This site may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com. To do this, ad networks place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.
www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com may use Google Analytics or other service providers to collect aggregate data in order to track site traffic statistics.
When you visit our website the server housing the pages automatically generates a "session log." We use session logs to help us determine how people travel through our site. In this way, we can structure our pages so that the information most frequently visited is easier to find. By tracking page visits, we can also determine if the information we're providing is being used. The only data gathered is the Internet Protocol (IP) address from which you came (which contains no personal information), the web site that referred you, the pages you visited and the date and time of those visits.
www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com uses Google geocoding web service application programming interface (API) to attempt to determine location of users in order to show "nearest" events of interest to them.
Users may be directed to www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com via banner ads or site links. Ads or site links that are placed by www.mrfracing.in use cookies or web beacons to deliver metrics on the effectiveness of the ads or links. They do not collect personal information from the user.
Sharing Your Information
www.mrftyres.com does not sell, rent, share or otherwise provide any of your information to anyone other than for site analytics as described in this policy.
Site metrics for www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com may be shared with other MRF Limited websites or subsidiaries or affiliates. The information shared will be aggregate data and will not include any of your personally identifiable information.
www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on MRF Limited or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of MRF Limited and this site; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of MRF Limited, its web sites, or the public.
Security of Your Information
Safeguarding information of visitors to our website is important to us. We use systems, policies and procedures to maintain accuracy of information and to protect information from loss, misuse or alteration.
Consent to Processing
By visiting this site and by providing your personally identifiable information to us, you understand and consent to the collection, use, processing, transfer, and disclosure of your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information globally including to the United States-in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Therefore, by visiting this site and by providing such information, you consent to the transfer of such information across country borders, and to the use, processing, and disclosure of such information in global locations as required. Your consent shall be deemed to include your consent to transfer of the personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information to locations that may have different levels of privacy protection than in your own country.
Links to Other Sites
www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com provides links to other websites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of all sites which you visit, including those whose links are provided so that you can understand how those sites collect, use and share your information.
www.mrftyres.com is not responsible for the privacy statements, content or data handling practices on other websites.
Children's Privacy
www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com does not knowingly intend to collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.
If a child has provided us with personal information a parent or guardian of that child may contact us at admin@mrftyres.com if they want this information deleted from our records. We will then make reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from the database that stores information for www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this online privacy statement for www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com,www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com privacy practices, or have any questions regarding the contents of this website please contact us at admin@mrftyres.com. www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com are committed to working with consumers to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any complaints or disputes about privacy and the handling of your data. www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com will be happy to respond to your questions and comments.
Privacy Statement Effective Date and Revision Days
Occasionally we may update the privacy statement for www.mrftyres.com and m.mrftyres.com in order to reflect any changes to the website or our privacy practices. If we update this statement, the new statement will be posted to the website ten (10) days prior to the changes taking effect. The effective date of this privacy statement is September 12th, 2013.
